{
    "id": "857c4822ed5147d5b706da7ad55dcbac",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mr. Cross was always angry ………………. his friends and family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He shouted ……………….. his wife and children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "So, they stayed away ………………… him as far as possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "One day, Mr. Cross was busy writing a letter. Just then a fly buzzed ……………. through the open window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He rushed ……………….. the fly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "away",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The fly flew into the kitchen and settled …………….. a pot of honey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Cross was trembling ……………….. anger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He picked up a rod and hit the fly heavily. But the fly was too quick …………….. Mr. Cross.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Wherever the fly went, Mr. Cross followed ………………. his ruler.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Everything went crashing ……………….. the floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}